Bare Bodkin Theatre Company Records UA230
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Bare Bodkin Theatre Company Records
2003 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Pen, Paint and Pretzels
Bare Bodkin Theatre Company
UA230
1.7 Linear Feet 2 boxes
127 Digital Object(s) Of the 127 digital objects, 117 have extent information and comprise 1,218 files.
4.41 Gigabytes Of the 127 digital objects, 117 have extent information and comprise 4.41 GB.
2 Web sites
This collection contains materials related to the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company, such as scripts, promotional posters and publications, administrative records, event recordings, and web crawls.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: I. Administrative materials; II. Productions; III. Web crawls; IV. Additional accessions; V. 2015 accessions; and VI. 2017 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in the spring of 2003, Bare Bodkin Theater Company is an organization dedicated to providing an outlet for student playwrights and directors to produce their work and other experimental works on and off campus. In addition to putting on student-written productions and writing workshops, Bare Bodkin hosts a 10-minute play festival every fall based on scripts from the Playwrighting I class. The name is taken from Mark Twain's The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn, and refers to threadless sewing needle head.
According to their constitution, the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company is charged with increasing the amount of experimental and student written and directed theatre throughout the Tufts' Medford/Somerville campus and in the surrounding communities as a means of generating more interest in the theatrical arts and supporting the incredible talents of primarily unrecognized artists. Additionally, there is a need on and off campus to provide theatre spaces for all interested directors. The company strives to accommodate the artistic visions of these students and to produce performances at Tufts that would otherwise not get the opportunity to perform because of their experimental nature.
All company members will be current Tufts students. Membership is awarded to students who attend one quarter of all general meetings, two of which can include the proposal meetings, and are involved in at least one company production.
Bare Bodkins is closely affiliated with the Pen, Paint, and Pretzels theater group, however, their funding is provided by the Tufts Community Union.
Custodial History
First transfer of materials to the DCA May, 2013.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials related to the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company, such as scripts, promotional posters and publications, administrative records, event recordings, and web crawls that date from 2003 -- 2019. Also included are artist in residence documents, constitutional changes, photographs, planning documents, and meeting minutes.
Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student Activities -- Performing Arts
- Administrative files, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.001; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records relating to the structure and administration of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company.
  Arrangement
  This collection is arranged by topic.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Constitution, 2003-01-19; MS230.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Board list, 2009; MS230.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Imagination Award, 2004; MS230.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Writing workshop sign-up, 2004-10; MS230.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Writing workshop announcement, 2005; MS230.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Writing workshop ideas, 2005; MS230.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Writing workshop sign-up, 2006; MS230.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Bare Bodkins Needs a Makeover, 2007; MS230.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Spring Production poster, 2008; MS230.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Writers Showcase submission guidelines, 2010 -- 2013; MS230.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Writers Showcase submission guidelines, 2009; MS230.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
- Productions, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.002; 1.7 Linear Feet; 8 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains records relating to the productions supported by Bare Bodkins, such as scripts, programs, posters, recordings, and publicity.
  This collection is arranged chronologically.
  - Undated scripts, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.002.001
    - For Spacious Skies or Taximan, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.002.001.00012; Foote, Doug (Box 1)
      scripts (documents)
    - In the Dark, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.002.001.00013; Yarsky, Michael (Box 1)
    - Love, Lexi, Love, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.002.001.00014; Coombs, Kris (Box 1)
    - Unidentified script, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - Will and Kit, 2003 -- 2013; UA230.002.001.00016; Tooney, Devin (Box 1)
  - 2003, Spring and Summer materials, UA230.002.002
    - Male and female actor in Pastoria, 2003; UA230.002.001.00017
      Written by George Saunders, directed by Marc Frost.
      Theater
    - Male actor in Pastoria, 2003; UA230.002.001.00018
    - Rehearsal for Strange Day, 2003; UA230.002.001.00019
      Written by Taylor Shann, directed by Marc Frost.
    - Reaching Critical Mass program, 2003-07-18 -- 2003-07-19; UA230.002.001.00020 (Box 1)
      Two One Act Plays: "The Siren Song of Stephen Jay Gould" by Benjamin Bettenbender and "Strange Day" by Taylor Shann.
      programs (documents)
  - 2003-2004 academic year productions, UA230.002.003
    - In the Blood cast photograph, 2003; UA230.002.001.00021
      Written by by Suzan-Lori Parks, directed by Marc Frost.
    - In the Blood program, 2003; UA230.002.001.00022 (Box 1)
    - A Light So Dim, 2004; UA230.002.001.00023; Shea, Brendan (Box 1)
  - 2004-2005 academic year productions, UA230.002.004
    - 24, 25, 26, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00024; Shea, Brendan (Box 1)
    - Churchyard Motel, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00025; Frost, Marc (Box 1)
    - Dismantling the 8-Ball?, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00026; Frost, Marc (Box 1)
    - Driving, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00027 (Box 1)
    - Shades of Ink Draw the Same Color, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00028; Frost, Marc (Box 1)
    - Summer, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - 2005-2006 academic year productions, 2004 -- 2006; UA230.002.005
    - Bodkin Madlib, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00030 (Box 1)
    - Bystander 911, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00031; Langsner, Meron (Box 1)
    - Dirty Story, 2004 -- 2005; UA230.002.001.00032 (Box 1)
      Narrative summary and production schedule.
    - Dirty Story rehearsal photographs, 2006-03; UA230.002.001.00033
    - Cast bonding photographs, 2006; UA230.002.001.00034
    - Unperformed or unworkshopped scrips, 2005 -- 2006; UA230.002.001.00035 (Box 1)
      b' Shalom by Meron Langsner; Untitled by Jeffrey Vanderkruik; Someone to Send Me Roses (2 versions) by Scott Weiner; Vanilla Chocolate Swirl by Scott Weiner; Tell Me Lies by Meron Langsner
    - Untitled by Jack, 2005 -- 2006; UA230.002.001.00036; Malia, Scott (Box 1)
  - 2006-2007 academic year productions, UA230.002.006
    - 'Mate, 2007; UA230.002.001.00037; Johnson, Caitlin (Box 1)
    - Sic, 2007; UA230.002.001.00038 (Box 1)
      See also Pen, Paint and Pretzels for more information on this play.
  - 2007-2008 academic year productions, UA230.002.007
    - Photos from Parents' Weekend, 2007; UA230.002.001.00039 (Box 1)
    - 24 Hour Theatre Festival posters, 2007 -- 2008; UA230.002.001.00040 (Box 1)
    - 24 Hour Theatre Festival scripts, 2007; UA230.002.001.00041 (Box 1)
    - 24 Hour Theatre Festival publicity articles, 2007; UA230.002.001.00042 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play posters, 2007; UA230.002.001.00043 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play program and scripts, 2007; UA230.002.001.00044 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play scripts, 2007; UA230.002.001.00045 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play scripts, 2007; UA230.002.001.00046 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play recordings, 2007; UA230.002.001.00047 (Box 1)
      DVD
    - Student performance recordings, 2007; UA230.002.001.00048 (Box 1)
      Mini-DV
    - Student performance recordings, 2007; UA230.002.001.00049 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play program, 2008; UA230.002.001.00050 (Box 1)
    - Self Evident program, 2008; UA230.002.001.00051 (Box 1)
    - Self Evident script, 2008; UA230.002.001.00052; Foote, Doug (Box 1)
    - Self Evident scripts - 3 drafts, 2008; UA230.002.001.00053; Foote, Doug (Box 1)
    - Self Evident performance recordings, 2008; UA230.002.001.00054; Foote, Doug (Box 1)
      DVD; Mini-DV
    - Self Evident musical accompaniment, 2008; UA230.002.001.00055 (Box 1)
      CD
    - Brenda gets naked and tells it like it is and Two Mommies scripts, 2007 -- 2008; UA230.002.001.00056 (Box 1)
    - The Invisible Hand of the Market, 2007 -- 2008; UA230.002.001.00057 (Box 1)
    - Just Press Play, 2007 -- 2008; UA230.002.001.00058; Hausmann, Joanna (Box 1)
    - Tell Me Lies, 2007 -- 2008; UA230.002.001.00059; Langsner, Meron (Box 1)
  - 2008-2009 academic year productions, UA230.002.008
    - 10 Minute Play Festival program, 2008 -- 2009; UA230.002.001.00060 (Box 1)
    - B.Y.O.T. Festival poster, 2008; UA230.002.001.00061 (Box 1)
      poster
    - Admotai, 2008 -- 2009; UA230.002.001.00062 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play poster, 2008; UA230.002.001.00063 (Box 1)
    - For Art's Sake, 2008 -- 2009; UA230.002.001.00064; Langsner, Meron (Box 1)
  - 2009-2010 academic year productions, UA230.002.009
    - Bonding, 2009 -- 2010; UA230.002.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - 2010-2011 academic year productions, UA230.002.010
    - Stories, 2010 -- 2011; UA230.002.001.00066; Stamell, Harrison (Box 1)
    - Writers Showcase excerpts, 2010 -- 2011; UA230.002.001.00067 (Box 1)
    - Writers Showcase program, 2011; UA230.002.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - 2011-2012 academic year productions, UA230.002.011
    - Play by Play DVD, 2011; UA230.002.001.00069 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play program and poster, 2011; UA230.002.001.00070 (Box 1)
    - Hamlet the Hip-Hopera program, 2011; UA230.002.001.00071 (Box 1)
    - Hamlet the Hip-Hopera photocall, 2011-11-21; UA230.002.001.00072
    - Over the Rainbow program, 2011-12-06; UA230.002.001.00073 (Box 1)
    - Over the Rainbow photocall, 2011-12-06; UA230.002.001.00074
    - Play by Play DVD, 2012-12-07; UA230.002.001.00075 (Box 1)
    - Romeo and Juliet program and poster, 2012; UA230.002.001.00076 (Box 1)
    - Romeo and Juliet DVD, 2012-04; UA230.002.001.00077 (Box 1)
  - 2012-2013 academic year productions, UA230.002.012
    - Yellowman production, 2013; UA230.002.001.00078 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play posters, 2012; UA230.002.001.00079 (Box 1)
    - Play by Play recording, 2012; UA230.002.001.00080 (Box 1)
    - 24 Play in a Day posters, 2012; UA230.002.001.00081 (Box Shared 137)
    - Poetry Reading, 2013; UA230.002.001.00082 (Box 1)
    - Lists of productions, 2012 -- 2013; UA230.002.001.00083 (Box 1)
    - Play in a Day scripts, 2012 -- 2013; UA230.002.001.00084 (Box 1)
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UA230.003; 2 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Bare Bodkin Theater Company website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Bare Bodkin Theatre Company, 2015 -- 2020; UA230.003.00001
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.
  - Bare Bodkin Theatre Company - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA230.003.00002; Bare Bodkin Theatre Company
    Frequency: quarterly crawl. (Inactive)
- Additional accessions, 2007 -- 2015; UA230.004
  - Administrative and production files, 2007 -- 2014; UA230-001
  - Administrative and production files, 2014 -- 2015; UA230-002
- 2015 accessions, circa 2007 -- 2015; UA230.000223; 53.65 Megabytes; 63 Digital Object(s) 63 digital objects comprising 1,158 files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Bare Bodkin Theatre Company, 2015, accessions 2016.018 and 2016.026.
  This series contains three subseries, Photographs and administrative files, circa 2007 -- 2013; Photographs and administrative files, 2013 -- 2014; and Administrative and production files. It is arranged in the order in which it was received.
  This series contains administrative and production files created by members of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company between 2007 and 2015. The bulk of the material is photographs of workshops, productions, and other events organized by the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company. The predominant file type in this series is JPEG.
  - Photographs and administrative files, circa 2007 -- 2013; UA230.000224; 14.22 Megabytes; 12 Digital Object(s) 12 digital objects comprising 171 files.
    Gift of Bare Bodkin Theatre Company, 2015, accession 2016.018.
    This sub-series contains administrative and production files created by members of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company between 2007 and 2013. The bulk of the material is photographs of workshops, productions, and other events organized by the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company.
    - Executive board member headshots, 2012 -- 2013; UA230.000225; 71 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - Con Men workshop photos, 2013 April 21; UA230.000226; 243.06 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Hamlet The Hip Hopera photos, 2011; UA230.000227; 32.67 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
    - Photos, circa 2007; UA230.000228; 796.4 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
    - Play in a Day photos, 2013 April 06; UA230.000229; 5.5 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 66 files.
    - Shakespeare Mad Lib photos, 2013 April 24; UA230.000230; 677.36 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - St. Patty's Day Limericks photos, 2013 March 13; UA230.000231; 4.01 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 35 files.
    - Stories of a Lifetime workshop photos, 2013 February 18; UA230.000232; 553.03 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 9 files.
    - Untitled Lindsay Carpenter workshop photos, 2013 May 10; UA230.000233; 148.17 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Valentine's Day Sonnets photos, 2013 February 14; UA230.000234; 1.34 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 13 files.
    - Loose files, 2007 -- 2013; UA230.000235; 938 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 9 files.
      This file contains several loose files that were not within an existing folder at the time of transfer.
  - Photographs and administrative files, 2013 -- 2014; UA230.000236; 39.43 Megabytes; 14 Digital Object(s) 14 digital objects comprising 183 files.
    This sub-series contains administrative and production files created by members of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company between 2013 and 2014. The bulk of the material is photographs of workshops, productions, and other events organized by the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company.
    - Artoun Festekjian's Hypnotism Show photos, 2013 October 20; UA230.000237; 1.36 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 17 files.
    - Executive Board member headshots, 2013 -- 2014; UA230.000238; 56.37 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - Jules and Monty workshop photos, 2013 September 22; UA230.000239; 199.52 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
    - Katabasis workshop photos, 2014 January 25; UA230.000240; 166.77 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Katabasis workshop photos, 2013 October 20; UA230.000241; 366.65 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
    - Mark and Avery Break-Up workshop photos, 2014 January 26; UA230.000242; 998.45 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Parents' Weekend performance photos, 2013 -- 2014; UA230.000243; 2.64 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 38 files.
    - Performing POEtry photos, 2013 October 20; UA230.000244; 1.09 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 15 files.
    - Play By Play photos, 2013 December 06; UA230.000245; 998.91 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 16 files.
    - Play in a Day photos, 2014 April 20; UA230.000246; 6.82 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 34 files.
    - Twelfth Night photos, 2014 April 04 -- 2014 April 06; UA230.000247; 6.62 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
    - Twelfth Night first read through photos, 2013 -- 2014; UA230.000248; 269.18 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - Loose files, 2013 -- 2014; UA230.000249; 17.9 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 20 files.
  - Administrative and production files, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000250; 937.37 Megabytes; 36 Digital Object(s) 36 digital objects comprising 804 files.
    Gift of Bare Bodkin Theatre Company, 2015, accession 2016.026.
    This series contains administrative and production files created by members of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company between 2014 and 2015. These records include photographs and planning documents related to workshops, productions, and other Bare Bodkin events; meeting minutes; logo redesign options; publicity photographs; production schedules; and constitutional changes. The predominant file type in this series is JPEG.
    - A Doll's House photo call, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000251; 335.69 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 133 files.
    - Actors in residence, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000252; 75.08 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Bodkin Major, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000253; 383 Megabytes; 17 Digital Object(s) 17 digital objects comprising 371 files.
      - Doctor Faustus, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000254; 386.12 Megabytes; 15 Digital Object(s) 15 digital objects comprising 368 files.
        - Director, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000255; 4.08 Megabytes; 2 Digital Object(s) 2 digital objects comprising 13 files.
          - General inspiration items, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000340; 3.8 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
        - Lights, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000256; 48.46 Megabytes; 4 Digital Object(s) 4 digital objects comprising 60 files.
          - Lights - equipment, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000257; 41.18 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 27 files.
          - Reference pictures, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000258; 7.24 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 27 files.
          - Research, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000259; 6.21 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
        - Photo call pictures, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000260; 294.97 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 183 files.
        - Producer - budget, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000261; 880.69 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
        - Production staff meeting minutes, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000262; 162.51 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
        - Props, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000263; 7.92 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
        - Puppets, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000264; 16.1 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 25 files.
        - Script, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000265; 16.75 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
        - Sound, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000266; 4.64 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
        - Stage management, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000267; 2.44 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 55 files.
      - Proposals, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000268; 4.82 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Logo redesign options, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000269; 591.85 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
    - Meeting minutes, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000270; 62.12 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
    - Play by Play, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000271; 8.49 Megabytes; 8 Digital Object(s) 8 digital objects comprising 28 files.
      - Auditions, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000272; 301.86 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
      - Play selection, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000273; 62.27 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
      - Play submissions, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000274; 7.86 Megabytes; 2 Digital Object(s) 2 digital objects comprising 12 files.
        - Grace Oberhofer - not using, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000275; 7.78 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
          This file contains music composed by Tufts student Grace Oberhofer, including sheet music and recordings.
      - Rehearsals, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000276; 6.19 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
      - Tech, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000277; 71.94 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
      - Writer-director publicity, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000278; 99.82 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
    - Poetry events, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000279; 562.2 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
    - Publicity pictures, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000280; 182.23 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 213 files.
    - Schwasty Shakespeare, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000281; 61.62 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
    - Survey, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000282; 14.61 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 files.
    - Twelfth Night photo call, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000283; 18 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
    - Workshops, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000284; 5.25 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 17 files.
    - Loose files, 2014 -- 2015; UA230.000285; 131 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
- 2017 accessions, 2015 -- 2017; UA230.000286; 3.42 Gigabytes; 54 Digital Object(s) 54 digital objects comprising 917 files.
  Gift of Bare Bodkin Theatre Company, 2017, accession UA-2020-048.
  This series is arranged in the order in which it was received.
  This series contains administrative and production files created by members of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company between 2015 and 2017. These records include photographs and planning documents related to workshops, productions, and other Bare Bodkin events; artists in residence documents; general interest meeting material; meeting minutes; and website content. The predominant file formats in this series include the following, in order of prevalence: JPEG, Word documents, Excel files, and MPEG.
  - 2015 -- 2016 academic year records, UA230.000287; 1.58 Gigabytes; 14 Digital Object(s) 14 digital objects comprising 196 files.
    This sub-series is arranged in the order in which it was received.
    This series contains administrative and production files created by members of the Bare Bodkin Theatre Company between 2015 and 2016. These records include photographs and planning documents related to workshops, productions, and other Bare Bodkin events; artists in residence documents; general interest meeting material; meeting minutes; and website content. The predominant file formats in this series include the following, in order of prevalence: Word documents, JPEG, and Excel files.